

□ (+44) 7488-769-169 | ■ peter789b@gmail.com | 希 Home Page | 回 GitHub | 面 tsun-to-gamedev

Summary_

Currently a Tool Programmer at Auroch Digital, I bring 5 years of industry experience and expertise in Unity.

Contributed to the release of titles on a beloved IP for Apple Arcade in the past, and have released titles in both desktop and mobile platforms. My well-rounded skill set also includes enterprise applications development.

Work Experience _____

Sumo Group - Auroch Digital

Bristol, United Kingdom

TOOL PROGRAMMER

Oct. 2022 - Now

- In charge of an in-house data editor to overcome Unity's limitation on game data management. Improving code team's efficiency, and supporting designer's need on complicated data editing while working with Perforce.
- Cooperated with artists and extended Unity's timeline tool to create cutscenes for Mars Horizon 2, reducing turnaround time for making important cinematic and key to deliver greenlight deck and announcement trailer
- Building a code generation tool for UI programmers. Improving programmer's efficiency and catching bugs before they surface in build.
- Created UI and core gameplay system for Mars Horizon 2 and contributing to main deliverables in milestones.

Q-Games Kyoto, Japan

GAME DEVELOPER

Nov. 2020 - Aug. 2022

- Cooperated with artists to create the main character in Frogger and the Rumbling Ruins, a well received title available on multiple platforms in Apple Arcade built with both Objective-C and Unity. Responsible for the player's scripting and majority of the UI.
- Helped maintain our in studio build machine with working experience in Jenkins and Mercurial SCM. Ensuring a timely delivery of stable weekly builds to our publisher.
- · Assisted in the release of a major update for Frogger in ToyTown, from introducing new features to bug fixing.

InCrowd Sports

Brighton, United Kingdom

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

Jun. 2018 - Sept. 2019

- Involved in development and maintenance for a large array of Android apps using Kotlin. Significant work including working with third party for authentication of premiere videos.
- Creating demo plugins with WPF and Unity for an industry leading LED display software built in C# to attract client's
 interest
- Experimented with Bitbucket Pipeline and Docker in the process of improving the build pipeline.

Tech Demo_

Procedural Tree Generation

MESH MANIPULATION, PROCEDURAL GENERATION

• Porting a tree generation algorithm invented by Nicholas McDonald to Unity. This is an experimental project to explore the possibilities of generating trees dynamically.

Ongoing Personal Project

UNITY, TOOL PROGRAMMING

• A prototype project which serves as a test ground for various experimentation. The project is under constant development and demonstrate my skill in Unity's tooling.

Education

University of Sussex

United Kingdom

B.Sc. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

· First class honours graduate with award winning performance, worked as a lab assistant to help teaching.